- Santa?
- Oh, hello, Sheldon.
(Santa:)You should be asleep.
(Sheldon:)Well, then you shouldn't have jingle bells
on your boots.
(Santa:)I've been wanting to talk to you.
(Santa:)I'm sorry I disappointed you
when you were a little boy.
(Santa:)I can do a lot of magical things...
(Santa:)...but unfortunately bringing
your Pop-Pop back isn't one of them.
- I understand.
- But I do have something special for you.
(Santa:)Close your eyes.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I hope it's a train.
(Santa:)Oh, it's better than a train.
(Sheldon:)Two trains?
(Sheldon:)Better.
- I'm getting three trains.
- Okay, open them.
(Santa:)This is for leaving me in the dungeon
to be eaten alive by ogres.
Now, hang on. In my defense...
Ho, ho, ho, you big dork.